This is a tale of adventure,
twenty-five years in the past.
It begins not long before the great
pirate era that we know of today.
Good ale! New skies! What a day!
It's been a joy traveling
these seas with you.
Thank you, Roger.
What are you going on about, you big dope?
Odin, we should be thanking you.
The whole stinking crew.
You're drinking too much again.
Dial it back.
Maybe.
If my doctor wasn't so
drunk, I'd listen to him.
Well, I'm drunk and I'm concerned
about your health, okay? Oh, bastard!
It was a cure for stupidity.
You need it, too!
Want some more?
I'm afraid I must return soon.
To the land of Wano?
Yes.
There's work left undone.
If it feels like too much to handle, you
don't have to tackle it on your own, okay?
If you need a hand, Odin, then this
clown will never let you down. Promise!
Yeah, right.
You'll be dead weight.
Don't kid yourself.
Hey, how about this?
I'll come along too and keep him in check.
Ray Lee, Ray Taro, Ogejiro,
I am grateful, but no.
The Kozuki must accomplish
this task alone.
For the last time!
Why is he Taro and I'm Giri?
Because only the cool kids get to be Taro.
I see that it's personal.
This journey taught me much, and
I'm grateful to have seen the world.
I have long questioned why my
country closed its borders.
I left the land of Wano by my own choice,
so I won't be so selfish as to ask
that they make me Shogun when I return.
But I will fight for my
cause, no matter what.
With the aid of my faithful retainers,
doubtless awaiting my return,
I shall open up the land of Wano.
Together we shall await the
coming of a new world in 20 years!
Are you sure you're ready? Yeah.
We shall not fail, Roger!
Now in the land of Wano, 25 years later...
Our lord is truly blessed, even the
weather itself shows him its favor.
Kyoshiro will look after
the capital and remain here.
You, deliver the message
quickly. Yes, sir!
Ah, the poor guy.
He'll be sad he's gonna miss the party.
This is Habu Port, located in Hakumai.
It is the largest port in the land
of Wano, and the most scenic as well.
Maple trees line its
massive wharf Framing the
entrance to the sea with
a splash of colors The red
and orange leaves fluttering
through the air Give
a festive send-off to
the boats as they depart
Let's start the party Bring some sake We
should drink and admire
the scenery Lord Orochi,
perhaps wait till you see Kaido
He doesn't care You
think he's not drunk too?
This is a banquet with 30,000 guests!
We're here to have a good time!
On the night of the annual Fire Festival,
the two leaders who rule the land of Wano
come together on the island of Onigashima.
There,
they throw a lavish
banquet attended by all of
Kaido's army and all of
Odochi's army as well.
Don't you stop?
Shut it up!
I'm not sure what's going on.
If you want to make the best,
I'll be afraid to put
the best you've ever seen.
We're creating the best for you.
We're living in a place.
I'm gonna let you go Dreaming
on! I'm gonna let you go.
Look at the place I'm going to have to!
I'm gonna make a move.
Let's go!
I'm gonna
dream it.
Dreaming on!
When you need a break
from dancing, eat up,
drink up, and when you're done,
get out there and dance some more.
It's the only day we're allowed to drink.
You better believe I'm going to
savor every last drop of this.
Can we go already?
You look fine.
Wait, my bangs are just not working.
Oh, my.
The sky is so clear tonight.
We should have a view of
the full moon in just a bit.
In the land of Wallow,
each region has different seasons
at different times of the year.
The weather also varies
tremendously by location.
Sunny skies in one region turn
to foreboding clouds in the next.
Thus, the rendezvous point at Tokage Port
looked quite different from the capital.
There's Nero, a single ship in sight!
Our 4,000 warriors are missing, too!
How could this be?
We conquered Udon.
Our men, they left the labor camp.
So where could they be now?
Blancing around there are
signs that the port was
attacked it appears the cat
couldn't make it in time
Smale is not responding
whatever has happened.
We cannot contact anyone
Twilight on the day of the
fire festival at Tokage port
This is the rendezvous
point without a doubt.
Why hasn't anyone come?
Where could they have disappeared?
To only a day has passed.
What could have befallen them?
What is going on here?
Sir Luffy Where have you gone?
Sir Hyogoro Please answer me?
Dog Storm's Musketeers
Sir Law Jabui Manokibi
Anyone We are the
retainers of Kozuki Odin.
We've come to settle the past.
20 years ago we failed to save our lord
and because we could not die by his side
that day we offer up our lives now in
hopes of seeing justice served at long last
however i must profess
that our lives are not
enough the enemy has 30
000 soldiers we need help!
I beg you!
Without your aid, we
shall all die in vain!
Please, answer me!
Help us reclaim our home! Stop! Enough!
Look!
This sky and this sea!
Heaven itself has abandoned us!
We'll find no aid from any place!
From any man!
Something terrible must have
happened to our friends!
Watch out! Coming through!
Don't just stand there, dance with us!
This is the one time of the
year you get to let loose!
Everybody start moving those feet!
There's a small boat here.
We can use it.
That's ridiculous, Dogstorm!
What are you saying?
We'll delay the plan! We must!
Alas, that is not an option, my lord.
Master King!
Shinobu, stop this.
We can't.
This is doomed to fail.
And yet it must be done.
You know this as well as I do.
It must be tonight The
night before the festival,
Odoshi had already thwarted their plans
Two days before the fire festival,
but hope still remained
Splendid,
we now have 4,200 soldiers I'm stunned
It's a miracle that they have joined us.
Attention, everyone.
Thank you for all of your hard work.
Please use the remaining time
for preparations and travel.
We'll meet at the
rendezvous port. Take care.
All right, we got them in 5,000 troops,
so get those ships in shape. Yes, sir.
Perfect.
You know the rendezvous port.
You know the time to be there.
Can you dig it?
No problem.
We'll see you there for sure.
Hell yeah.
Then we'll split for now.
We're meeting up with our
friends in Amigasa Village.
On the day of the festival, we'll
sail into battle on the sunny.
The other boats are up to you. Got it.
We'll work hard and work fast.
You taught us a lot.
You're awesome. Damn straight.
Kaido won't even know what hit him.
Just two more days and
we're gonna kick some ass.
We don't have enough timber.
Cut up anything made of
wood that you can find.
We can count on Ocho's group to bring
swords and other weapons from Ringo.
What's next?
We'll put together some armor
from the enemy's supplies.
I don't know if we can use these or not?
But the factory here still has a ton of
heavy weapons they were going to sell!
Good
If we arrive at the meeting place early,
then we might draw too much
attention to ourselves.
Look, that morning the Shogun's procession
will travel to the port along this path.
But as soon as the Shogun's ship leaves,
everyone in the capital
will start partying.
Once they're distracted, then we gather.
Easy enough.
We'll get there right before twilight
at the second hour of the bird.
Some officials are staying on the
mainland, so we have to be careful.
We can't let them report to Onigashima!
Silence them if you have to! All right!
It's really okay to take these! Whoa!
This one's cool!
Usopp will be jealous when he sees this!
We'll be samurai!
You are up against Kaido.
Are you certain you are prepared for this?
That loser!
He can't stop me!
I'll slice Kaido in half!
We didn't come all this way just to lose.
My blade hungers for victory!
They make such an awesome samurai!
They're cute, like bugs.
They're horned beetles.
You should really wear some armor, too.
No, that stuff slows me down.
You need it, hmm?
You guys with the low bounties are frail.
And mouth!
Don't you test me!
I'll put a boat up your ass!
Go ahead, try!
What are you idiots doing?
Apparently it's winter at the entrance
of Onigashima, so Orochi said.
Oh, it'll be cold?
And what do you gotta mean by entrance?
Maybe Onigashima has unpredictable
weather like the rest of Wano?
Either way, the cold shouldn't be a
problem since we're covered in fur.
True.
Tis not the season that's our concern.
It's the forecast!
There's supposed to be
a full moon that night,
but if it's hidden behind the
clouds, that won't help us.
Oh, that's right!
If all the other minks transform like you,
then this raid will be a walk in the park!
Our transformations are
always a bit of a gamble.
If Master Cat Viper and the
Guardians arrive in time,
they're still going to be the
greatest asset that we've got.
What's wrong, Luffy?
It bugs me that Big Mom is here.
Cause Jinbei hasn't shown up yet.
And that's extra bad!
Since he's the one who fought her.
So we could escape.
I'll be waiting for you and Wano.
You better show up!
My deepest gratitude.
Jinbei.
Don't die no matter what. Got it?
He settled things with Big Mom.
He was gonna join our crew!
And we'll be happy to have him we've still
got some time he'll come he wouldn't die.
Yeah, you're right!
He'll be here.
Hey guys, come look we got
a gift from Ushimitsu Koza?
I didn't hear about a
robbery in the capital.
Well, whatever the story is, he's
the only person who would do this.
Shame we can't take part
in the Fire Festival.
But now we can at least buy fresh water.
We burned down the bandits' hideout
because they stole our food.
I thought they'd come seeking
revenge and we'd wipe them out.
But instead, they keep stealing
more food than ever before!
I'm thinking you might have
something to do with all this.
We don't know anything!
I heard an army of samurai are
planning to make a big raid.
Do you think that's why
they're stealing food?
I don't know, but don't let him hear that!
Hey!
What are you muttering about?
Please, allow me! I'll show you!
There's no need for any of
these people to be hurt.
Hotsuru!
Show me?
So you're saying you know
what happened to the food?
You'll see once we get there.
It's a bit far, though.
If you need that much food, you
must have recruited many allies.
You're here, aren't you, Keen?
You've returned to the land of Wano!
I was stunned when I saw Kikunojo.
Don't worry, Keen.
You can rely on me.
I will draw the attention of our enemies.
Your secret is safe.
I won't let them find you
Save this country!
Bring back the glory of the Kozuki clan!
Otsuru, stop this!
You don't have to cover for us!
It's all right now.
All we wanted was to eat our
fill even once before we died!
Does that mean you bastards did it?
Ah, Koza!
You can all say hello
to your lord in hell!
Did you find the ship? Yes, sir!
It's in sight right now!
Sure you want us to let
loose on this thing?
I told you to do it, so do it already!
Burn it!
Roger!
Missing, complete!
You really thought I'd
let you have your way?
I am the Shogun!
No, the bridges!
The great bridge between Koby
and Udon has been destroyed.
Don't stop there!
The great bridge between Koby
and Udon has been destroyed.
This is what you get?
What the hell happened?
Someone just blew up the bridge.
We can't get to the other side.
Something's wrong.
The enemy must have discovered our plan.
All that remains is the port.
We destroyed every ship in
the port as you ordered, sir.
Excellent.
We'll rebuild everything.
Once this is over, unfortunately,
I've yet to see the Akasaya
samurai or any of the
troops they've recruited but
I know they're out there.
The tale of the samurai
who traveled through
time from 20 years in the past of course,
no one believed that story but perhaps
they will when I show them one?
their heads.
No, even if I did show them,
it's too strange to believe.
Yasui knew exactly what he was
doing.
He made it sound even more ridiculous.
But my information is credible.
The Akasaya
members are indeed alive.
I don't care if everyone in this
blasted country thinks I've gone mad.
I have the authority to
do as I please either way.
Not only did I destroy their ships,
I've blocked every last route to Cage?
Port.
4,000 troops.
You did a splendid job.
But not a single one of them is
making it to that port tomorrow.
You won't even get a chance
to exact your revenge.
I'll kill you again, Ghost of Akazaya!
Ha!
Follow in despair!
See how truly helpless you are!
Stop the sadness!
You can't take that boat!
All of you will die insane!
We should turn back! We can regroup!
Let's wait for another chance!
We cannot throw away this opportunity.
The chance you speak of will
not occur for another year.
Soon they will discover that
we've taken control of Udon.
There will be nowhere left for us to hide.
Not anymore.
Kaido will use the full
strength of his army
to hunt down every last
rebel in the country.
We can't keep stealing their food.
They'll catch on soon enough.
You heard what happened before
we departed from Kuri, right?
The people of Okobore Town believed in
us and took the blame for our crimes.
They were burned alive.
Among them was my wife.
Please allow us to go.
I will not.
You want us to flee?
Live in disgrace?
You would deny us even our dignity?
But what will become of me?
We want you to live, of
course, alongside Lady Yuri.
You're saying that you want to abandon me?
Your father began without a
single supporter to his name.
We were lucky, and we are grateful
that we were able to meet him.
He took a bunch of fools and turned them
into samurai because he believed in us.
So we are here as retainers to our Lord,
and I shall proudly fight in his
name, to the bitter end, if need be.
Don't go!
You can't leave me, Kin'emon! Please!
I can't stand to lose anyone else!
Listen up, all of you.
This country has been
isolated for centuries.
As its stewards, it is a decision
deeply tied to the Kozuki clan.
But the times are changing.
This world will soon enter a new era.
Before this comes to pass, our land
of Wano must be prepared to meet it!
We must open our borders!
The tale of Odin begins 41
years ago in the Flower Capital.
Kozuki Odin has returned!
Hide your wives quickly,
and your daughters too!
Hide the livestock quick,
hide the livestock!
Looks like his latest escape
plan must have failed.
What is wrong with you?
Don't you ever learn?
The man was well known in the
capital but not always well liked.
Damn it, I can't breathe!